[{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678979564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":20186,"timeElapsed":173873},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678997950,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":18385,"timeElapsed":192259},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679019470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":21518,"timeElapsed":213779},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679031683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":12213,"timeElapsed":225992},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679056250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":24566,"timeElapsed":250559},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679066317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":10066,"timeElapsed":260626},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679075710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":9392,"timeElapsed":270019},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679085114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":9402,"timeElapsed":279422},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679094388,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":9273,"timeElapsed":288697},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679133375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":34510,"timeElapsed":327684},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679142328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":8951,"timeElapsed":336637},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679156385,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":14056,"timeElapsed":350694},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679168170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":11784,"timeElapsed":362479},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679174244,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":6073,"timeElapsed":368553},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679183947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":9702,"timeElapsed":378256},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679188342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4394,"timeElapsed":382650},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679195590,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":7247,"timeElapsed":389899},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679200855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5264,"timeElapsed":395164},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679206351,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5495,"timeElapsed":400660},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679245194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":36451,"timeElapsed":439503},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679250721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5526,"timeElapsed":445030},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679254350,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3628,"timeElapsed":448659},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679256976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2625,"timeElapsed":451285},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679266522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":9544,"timeElapsed":460831},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679270734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4211,"timeElapsed":465043},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679278793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8058,"timeElapsed":473102},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679288199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":9404,"timeElapsed":482507},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679291490,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3291,"timeElapsed":485799},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679307424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":14377,"timeElapsed":501733},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679312817,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5392,"timeElapsed":507126},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679322184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":9366,"timeElapsed":516493},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679324771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2586,"timeElapsed":519080},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679327941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3169,"timeElapsed":522250},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679330524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2582,"timeElapsed":524833},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679337819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":7294,"timeElapsed":532128},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679343778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5958,"timeElapsed":538087},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679350320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"9","question":"For what in your life do you feel most grateful?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":6541,"timeElapsed":544629},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679387372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":33989,"timeElapsed":581681},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679389702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2329,"timeElapsed":584011},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679393334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3631,"timeElapsed":587643},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679396676,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3341,"timeElapsed":590985},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679402216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5539,"timeElapsed":596525},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679404418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2201,"timeElapsed":598727},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679411266,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":6847,"timeElapsed":605575},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679414102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2835,"timeElapsed":608411},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679418523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4420,"timeElapsed":612832},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679434693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":14285,"timeElapsed":629002},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679442280,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":7586,"timeElapsed":636589},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679447792,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5511,"timeElapsed":642101},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679450215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2421,"timeElapsed":644524},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679464088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":13872,"timeElapsed":658397},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679466374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2285,"timeElapsed":660683},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679470402,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":4027,"timeElapsed":664711},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679473526,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3123,"timeElapsed":667835},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679479942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6415,"timeElapsed":674251},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679489221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":7790,"timeElapsed":683530},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679491209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":1987,"timeElapsed":685518},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679497448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6239,"timeElapsed":691757},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679500426,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2977,"timeElapsed":694735},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679504504,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4077,"timeElapsed":698813},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679506267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1763,"timeElapsed":700576},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679511390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":5122,"timeElapsed":705699},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679513935,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2543,"timeElapsed":708243},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679519129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5194,"timeElapsed":713438},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679530138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":9637,"timeElapsed":724447},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679532075,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":1935,"timeElapsed":726384},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679540496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":8420,"timeElapsed":734805},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679543842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3345,"timeElapsed":738151},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679555593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":11749,"timeElapsed":749902},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679557148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1554,"timeElapsed":751457},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679566398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":9249,"timeElapsed":760706},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679574517,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8118,"timeElapsed":768826},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679581789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7271,"timeElapsed":776098},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679584773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2983,"timeElapsed":779082},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679602955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":16717,"timeElapsed":797264},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679605885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2928,"timeElapsed":800194},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679608475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2589,"timeElapsed":802784},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679610635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2159,"timeElapsed":804944},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679617666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7030,"timeElapsed":811975},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679619566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1899,"timeElapsed":813875},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679623619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":4051,"timeElapsed":817928},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679627014,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3394,"timeElapsed":821323},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679633549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6534,"timeElapsed":827858},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679647772,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":12705,"timeElapsed":842081},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679650484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2711,"timeElapsed":844793},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679654955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":4469,"timeElapsed":849264},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679657628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2673,"timeElapsed":851937},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679663784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6155,"timeElapsed":858093},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679665294,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1509,"timeElapsed":859603},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679668306,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":3011,"timeElapsed":862614},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679671027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2720,"timeElapsed":865336},{"subjectID":"npry5g6c6m","prolificID":"670ee6d9ec858a5854c2e4f2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3ec5379fef41d04369","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679675116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4089,"timeElapsed":869425}]